We have lost CTRL.
Warning is a science fiction film directed by Agata Alexander.
Loneliness, death and the meaning of life, explored through vastly separate
lives colliding in interweaving short stories set in future Earth.
David, played by Thomas Jane.
Ben, played by Patrick Schwarzenegger.
The Voice of God, played by James D'Arcy.
Brian, played by Tomasz Kot.
Olivia, played by Toni Garrn.
Charlie, played by Rupert Everett.
Warning is a 2021 science fiction thriller film directed by Agata Alexander in her
directorial debut, from a screenplay by Alexander, Jason Kaye and Rob Michaelson.
It stars Alex Pettyfer, Alice Eve, Annabelle Wallis, Benedict Samuel, Charlotte Le Bon, Thomas Jane,
Patrick Schwarzenegger, Rupert Everett, Tomasz Kot, Kylie Bunbury and Garance Marillier.
The film premiered at the 2021 Sitges Film Festival.
The tone is thought_provoking.